A Finding Aid to the Rosamund Felsen Gallery Records, 1949-2014, bulk 1978-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1949-2013; bulk 1978-2006; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 19.7 Linear feet Box 2-22, OV 34
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, "In + Out City Limits," Posters and Photographs, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 34)
  - Rhoades, Jason, 1993-1999, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rhoades, Jason, Printed Material, 1993-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - Rhoades, Jason, Slides, Photographs and Transparencies, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
  - Rhoades, Jason, Slides, Photographs and Transparencies, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
  - Rice, Leland, 1978-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Rice, Leland, Printed Material, 1979-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rice, Leland, Slides and Photographs, 1977-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Roberts, Marcia, Slides, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Rogers, Steve, 1984-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Rogers, Steve, Printed Material, 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Rogers, Steve, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1980-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
  - Rogers, Steve, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1978-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
  - Rosenfeld, Marina, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rothenberg, Erika, 1987-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rothenberg, Erika, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1988-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
  - Rothenberg, Erika, Projects, 1988, 2000-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Rothenberg, Erika, Printed Material, 1985-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9-11)
  - Rothenberg, PhotographsErika, 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - Roysdon, Emily, 2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, Exhibition at Felsen Gallery, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Ruppersberg, Allen, Slides and Photographs, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
  - Sanchez, Pauline Stella, Slides, 1989-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
  - Sanchez, Pauline Stella, Transparencies, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Serrano, Evelyn, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Shaw, Jim, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Shaw, Jim, "Dream Drawings", 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shaw, Jim, Copies of Drawings, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Shaw, Jim, In Residence at Felsen Gallery, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Shaw, Jim, Exhibition at Felsen Gallery, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Shaw, Jim, Las Vegas, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Shaw, Jim, Printed Material, 1980s-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10-12)
  - Shaw, Jim, Slides, "Everything Must Go", 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Sklar, Keith, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Sklar, Keith, Slides and Transparencies, 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Alexis, 1978-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - Smith, Alexis, and Heidi Hardin, "Stardust", 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sonnier, Keith, 1978-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Sonnier, Keith, Printed Material, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sonnier, Keith, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1970s-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - Syrop, Mitchell, 1992-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Syrop, Mitchell, Poster, "All Men Are Created Equal...but only machines have guarantees", 1982; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 34)
  - Syrop, Mitchell, Printed Material, 1983-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Syrop, Mitchell, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1980s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7-13)
  - Tanaka, Haruko, 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD and one DVD. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Thornycroft, Ann, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Thornycroft, Ann, Transparencies, 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Tottenham, John, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Tucker, Brian, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, 1981-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Machines and Articles (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, LAICA Show, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, The Icelandic Women and the King of Tonga (1987), 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, "The Kelver Training Cow", 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Jeffrey Vallance Presents the Richard Nixon Museum (1991), 1971-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Three's a Shroud (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Exhibitions and Projects, 1983-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Texts and Writings, 1980s-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Printed Material, 1980s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14-17)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Printed Material, 1979-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Vallance, Jeffrey, Slides, Photographs, Transparencies, and Negatives, 1960s-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5-10)
  - Weber, Marnie, 1997-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Weber, Marnie, Exhibitions, 1997-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD and one DVD. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Weber, Marnie, "The Ghost Trees", 2003; Archival Resource Key; 2 Electronic discs (DVD) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Weber, Marnie, "The Spirit Girls, Songs that Never Die", 2005; Archival Resource Key; 2 Electronic discs (DVD) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Weber, Marnie, Printed Material, 1997-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Weber, Marnie, Slides, 1997-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Wegman, William, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Dee, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Artists, Miscellaneous, 1970s-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes four CDs, two DVDs, and one floppy disk. (Box 22, Folder 7-10)
- Exhibitions and Event Files, 1979-2014; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 3.7 Linear feet Box 22-25, OV 34-36
  Files relating to Rosamund Felsen Gallery exhibitions and performances include artist resumes, consignment and sales records, check lists, photographs and slides, drafts and mock-ups, born digital material, price lists, installation directions, and printed material such as catalogs, announcements, and clippings. Also included in this series are files relating to art fairs, exhibitions, trips, and performances held at other museums and galleries. Folders might include sales records, event itineraries, ephemera, slides and photographs, and printed material.
  - Events and Exhibitions Held at Rosamund Felsen Gallery, Archival Resource Key
    - Heterodox (1987), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Just Pathetic (1990), Curated by Ralph Rugoff, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
    - Presenting Rearwards (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14-17)
    - Rosamund Felsen Clinic and Recovery Center (1992), Curated by Ralph Rugoff, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18-20)
    - Go Downstairs Diagonally (1993), Curated by Paul McCarthy, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Paintings of the '80s (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Roy Dowell, Paul McCarthy, and Renee Petropoulos, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Be Specific (1996), Curated by Michael Duncan, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - The Vegas Show (1997), Curated by Jeffrey Vallance, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Alonso Mateo and Cisco Jimenez, 1997; Archival Resource Key; Includes one floppy disk. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Chairs, Plazas, Faces, Gardens, Rooms (1998), Curated by William Leavitt, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - i candy: LA in Flux (1998), Curated by John Boskovich, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Project Wall: Ingrid Calame (1998), Curated by Steven Hull, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Project Wall: Minimundus (1999), Curated by Georgina Starr, 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Project Wall: Not Photography (1999), Curated by Sam Durant, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Project Wall: Melissa Thorne (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Project Wall: Dave Muller (1999), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Project Wall: Simon Leung/Nils Norman (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Project Wall: Erwin Wurm (1999), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Project Wall: Landscape Memories (1999), Curated by Steven Hull, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Project Wall: Expanding Limited Space (1999), Curated by Andrea Bowers, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Project Wall Exhibitions, General Papers, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Odd Gloss (1999), Curated by Gordon Haines, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Art/Journalism (1999), Curated by Laurence A. Rickels, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Touring the Frame (1999), Curated by Charles Gaines, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Monique van Genderen, Bart Exposito, Jacques de Beaufort, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Karl Haendel, Richard Kraft, Mitchell Syrop, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - LAPD: Pattern and Decoration in Los Angeles (2003), Curated by Michael Duncan, Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
    - Who's Who? 6 Bay Area Artists (2005), Archival Resource Key; Includes two CDs. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - A Play on Action: 5 Los Angeles Artists Consider Feminism (2006), Curated by Bari Ziperstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Feminism: Legacies and Reinventions; Mary Kelly: Love Songs (2006), Archival Resource Key; 2 Electronic discs (DVD) (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - The Book Shop (2013), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Exhibitions Check Lists, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Group Exhibition Check List, 1987-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29-30)
    - Printed Material, Felsen Gallery Announcement Cards, 1979-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Printed Material, Felsen Gallery Posters, 1979, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 34)
    - Printed Material, Felsen Gallery Posters, 2006-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Events and Exhibitions, Other Locations, Archival Resource Key
    - Chicago Art Fair, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - I.C.A.F. LA Art Fair, 1986; 1987, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
    - Venice Biennale 1988, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Visit to Castello Di Rivara, Photographs, 1992 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Venice Biennale 1993, Photographs, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Song Poems (2002), Angstrom Gallery, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Armory Show 2003, 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Art Basel Miami Beach 2003, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Frieze Art Fair 2004, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Mexico International Contemporary Art Fair 2004, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles, 1955-1985 (2006), Centre Pompidou, Paris, France, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Art Miami 2007, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - LA Art in New York 2007, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Pulse Contemporary Art Fair 2009, New York, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - ARCO Madrid 2010, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Pulse Contemporary Art Fair 2012, Miami, 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Texas Contemporary Art Fair, 2012; 2013; 2014, 2012-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Pulse Miami 2014, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Prospect .1 New Orleans (2008), 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Art Fairs, Domestic, 1990-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Art Fairs, International, 1990-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
    - Event and Exhibition Posters, Others, 1977-2001; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 35)
    - Event and Exhibition Posters, Others, 1981, 1992; Archival Resource Key; Includes numbered edition poster from Orestes and the Three Furious Ladies (1981) at the Barnsdall Gallery. (Oversize 36)
  - Mixed Exhibitions and Events, Photographs, Slides, and Images, 1990-2000s; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD (Box 25, Folder 6-11)
- Financial Records, 1978-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 3.5 Linear feet Box 25-29
  This series is composed mostly of the gallery's account records. Folders include sales records, scant correspondence, invoices, and receipts.
  - Accounts Payable, 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 12-15)
  - Accounts Payable, 1990-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1-9)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1978-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 10-14)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1986-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1-13)
  - Accounts Receivable, 1997-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1-13)
  - Accounts Receivable, 2012-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Accounts Receivable, Unnumbered Invoices, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sales, Revolutions Per Minute (The Art Record), 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Rights and Reproductions, 1992, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5)